(Howard:)Damn his Vulcan hearing.
(Leonard:)Not a good time, Sheldon.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SHELDON:
Penny. Penny. Penny.
Ugh, this is ridiculous.
[LEONARD GROANS]
(Sheldon:)-What?
-Hello, Penny.
(Sheldon:)I realize you're currently at the mercy
of your biological urges...
...but as you have a lifetime of poor
decisions ahead, may I interrupt this one?
(Penny:)Great to see you too. Come on in.
(Sheldon:)Wolowitz has informed me
of your grand deception.
Do you have anything to say?
(Leonard:)Yes, I feel terrible about it.
I will never forgive myself.
I don't expect you to. I'd appreciate it
if you'd leave me with Penny...
(Leonard:)...for a session of self-criticism
and repentance.
Can someone tell me
what's going on here?
(Sheldon:)What's going on is I was led to believe
I was making strides in science...
(Sheldon:)...when in fact
I was being fed false data...
(Sheldon:)...at the hands of Wolowitz, Koothrappali
and your furry little boy toy.